Sara Au

519 Scott Street Fremont, CA 94539

(925) 663-5609 au.sara.c@gmail.com

Responsible Behavior Technician experienced in performing ABA therapy for children with developmental disorders. Passionate and motivated with a drive for excellence in professional work. 1 year and 5 months as a Behavior Therapist and 10 months as a Vision Therapist Assistant.

EXPERIENCE

Happy Hour 4 Kids, *Behavior Therapist*SEP 2016 - APR 2017 — New York City, NY

- Manage challenging behavior of children
 with socioemotional, developmental, and related disorders in classroom and 1:1 setting
- Collect, graph, and update behavior skills data and programs
- Teach new skills using Discrete Trial Teaching and Natural Environmental Teaching

Center for Autism, Behavior Therapist

AUG 2015 - MAR 2016 — Fremont, CA

- Provide intensive ABA therapy in two to
 five hour sessions unique to client under Supervisor
- Skillfully record and graph behavior and skills data in iPad logbooks

C&A Behavior Consulting, Behavior Therapist

MAR - JUN 2016 — Fremont, CA

Fulfilled requirements for Registered Behavior Technician (RBT)

Successfully implemented Differential Reinforce ment and behavior extinction for maladaptive behavior while teaching more appropriate behavior

Kageyama Vision, Vision Therapist Assistant FEB - NOV 2014 — Campbell, CA

Performed over 30 vision therapy activities for children with dyslexia, autism, and other disabilities to improve eye-muscle coordination and academic skills

- Record patient progress and data during therapy sessions run by Vision Therapist
- Accurately documented and filed therapist assessment, treatments, and follow-ups of clients

SKILLS

- Self-motivated
- Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Google Docs
- Quick learner in fast-paced environment
- Applied Behavior Analysis
- Professionalism and customer service

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Private Math Tutor for 4th Grader

MAR - JUN 2016 - Fremont, CA

Activities Assistant for Seniors

SEP 2014 - JUN 2015 - Fremont, CA

Lead High-School Teacher

OCT 2014 - Baja California

Volunteer

OCT - DEC 2013 - San Jose, CA

EDUCATION

San Jose State University, B.S. in Health Science SEP 2016 - APR 2017 — San Jose, CA

CERTIFICATIONS

- **Board Certified Behavior Technician (BCAT)**
- DEC 2015-2017
- Registered Behavior Technician (RBT)
- MAY 2016-2018
- **CPR Certified**
- SEP 2016

LANGUAGES

• Fluent in English, Cantonese

Links

• linkedin.com/in/sara-au